Guide to the Richard Charles Lee Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1934-1969; Series II; 3.75 linear feet (9 boxes)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1956-1967 (Box 108, Folder 1947)
  - Durden, Dennis, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 1948)
  - Einhorn, Joseph, 1959-1965, undated (Box 108, Folder 1949)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1960 (Box 109, Folder 1950)
  - Feiss, Carl: Report on New Haven Redevelopment Program, 1955, 1960, undated (Box 109, Folder 1951)
  - Fire Department, 1954-1967 (Box 109, Folder 1952)
  - Flower lists, 1966-1969, undated (Box 109, Folder 1953)
  - Fleming, Robert Ingersoll, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 1954)
  - Ford Foundation, 1962-1968 (Box 109, Folder 1955-1956)
  - Giaimo, Robert N., 1956-1969 (Box 109, Folder 1957-1961)
  - Golden, John M., 1949-1964 (Box 109, Folder 1962-1964)
  - Grapevine Press, 1958-1961 (Box 110, Folder 1965-1966)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1953-1962 (Box 110, Folder 1967)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney: printed material, 1959-1963 (Box 110, Folder 1968)
  - Harper's Magazine: "Lee of New Haven", 1957 (Box 110, Folder 1969)
  - Harrison, Henry, 1961-1962 (Box 110, Folder 1970)
  - Healey, Arthur, 1657 (Box 110, Folder 1971)
  - Hill Neighborhood Union: Norman Fund, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 1972)
  - Holiday article, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 1973)
  - Honorary degrees: Rollins College, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 1974-1975)
  - Honorary degrees: Saint Lawrence University, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 1976)
  - Humorous, 1953-1969, undated (Box 110, Folder 1977-1979)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1960-1967 (Box 110, Folder 1980)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 1981)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1958-1965 (Box 110, Folder 1982-1983)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1967-1968 (Box 111, Folder 1984)
  - Kaplan, Jacob, 1962-1966 (Box 111, Folder 1985)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1964-1969 (Box 111, Folder 1986)
  - Kennedy, Edward M.: photographs, undated (Box 111, Folder 1987)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1963 (Box 111, Folder 1988-1989)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1957-1968 (Box 111, Folder 1990-1991)
  - Kennedy, Robert F.: photographs, undated (Box 111, Folder 1992)
  - Lee, Richard C., 1950-1969 (Box 111, Folder 1993-1995)
  - Lee, Richard C.: biographical data, 1960-1966 (Box 111, Folder 1996)
  - Lee, Richard C.: general correspondence, 1934-1964, undated (Box 112, Folder 1997)
  - "The Sally Lee", undated (Box 112, Folder 1998)
  - Lee, Sally and David, undated (Box 112, Folder 1999-2000)
  - Lee, Tara, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 2001)
  - Logue, Edward J., 1954-1969 (Box 112, Folder 2002)
  - Levine material, 1955-1965 (Box 112, Folder 2003)
  - Lohmann, Carl A., 1945-1957 (Box 112, Folder 2004)
  - Lord and Tyler, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 2005)
  - Macy's, 1957-1963 (Box 112, Folder 2006)
  - Macy's presentation material, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 2007)
  - Macy's press kit, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 2008)
  - Mayors of New Haven, undated (Box 112, Folder 2009)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954-1969 (Box 112, Folder 2010-2011)
  - Moffitt, John, 1962-1963 (Box 112, Folder 2012)
  - Moses, Robert, 1956-1967 (Box 113, Folder 2013)
  - Mulvey, Harold Campaign: personal, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 2014)
  - National League of Cities, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 2015)
  - N. A. A. C. P., 1958-1961 (Box 113, Folder 2016-2017)
  - Negro participation, 1954-1963 (Box 113, Folder 2018)
  - New Haven Railroad, 1961, undated (Box 113, Folder 2019)
  - News clips, 1956-1961 (Box 113, Folder 2020)
  - Overview, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 2021)
  - Paquin and education, 1964-1965 (Box 113, Folder 2022-2023)
  - Personnel, 1959-1962, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 2024)
  - Photographs, 1956, 1962, 1964-1965, undated (Box 113, Folder 2025)
  - Police Department, 1963-1968, undated (Box 113, Folder 2026-2028)
  - Powder House Day, 1957, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 2029)
  - Quayle, Oliver, 1966, 1969 (Box 114, Folder 2030)
  - Riots, racial matters, 1959-1968 (Box 114, Folder 2031-2033)
  - Register: Jacksons, Leeney, etc., 1957-1967 (Box 114, Folder 2034)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham A., 1957-1958, 1969, undated (Box 114, Folder 2035)
  - Rutgers, 1962-1963 (Box 114, Folder 2036)
  - Sargent and Company, 1956-1958 (Box 114, Folder 2037)
  - Sheriffs, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 2038)
  - Shriver, R. Sargent, 1957-1964 (Box 114, Folder 2039)
  - Sit-outs, 1960 (Box 114, Folder 2040)
  - Snow storm procedures, undated (Box 114, Folder 2041)
  - Stores for Church and Chapel Streets, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 2042)
  - Skemp, Robert: portraits, 1956, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 2043)
  - Smith (Bruce Smith Report), 1958 (Box 114, Folder 2044)
  - State Street Project, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 2043)
  - Statistics, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 2044)
  - Stevens, Roger, 1955-1963, undated (Box 114, Folder 2045)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1955-1964, undated (Box 115, Folder 2046)
  - Talbot book reviews, 1966, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 2047)
  - Task Force, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 2048)
  - Tax Study: Barry Passett, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 2049)
  - Truman, Harry, 1958-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2050)
  - Turnkey housing, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 2051)
  - Unions, 1956, undated (Box 115, Folder 2052)
  - Urban renewal, 1957, 1959, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 2053)
  - Vista, 1962-1963 (Box 115, Folder 2054)
  - West Rock Tunnel, 1951-1954, undated (Box 115, Folder 2055)
  - White House Mail, 1960-1964 (Box 115, Folder 2056)
  - White House pen, undated (Box 115, Folder 2057)
  - Whitney, Clarence, 1959-1961 (Box 115, Folder 2058)
  - Yale: miscellaneous, 1955, 1958-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2060-2061)
- Campaign Files, 1945-1973; Series III; 6 linear feet (15 boxes)
  This series primarily contains materials documenting Lee's mayor campaigns between 1949 and 1967. The series also includes material on state and national elections for 1956, 1958, and 1960, with smaller amounts for later elections. This series should be of considerable relevance to those interested in political campaigns and the electoral process. Mayor Lee effectively used the radio and television media in his successful campaign efforts and is noteworthy because he was one of the first politicians to make extensive use of modern polling techniques. See the files for surveys and polls in 1955, 1956, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1964, 1967, and 1968.
  The arrangement for Series III is chronological by campaign and then alphabetical by subject or person for each electoral contest.
  - Murphy vs. Celentano, 1945 (Box 116, Folder 2062)
  - Addresses., 1947, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2063)
  - Biography, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2064)
  - Campaign clippings, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2065)
  - Campaign history: Lee vs. Celentano, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2066)
  - Convention, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2067)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2068-2069)
  - Election results, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2070)
  - Endorsements, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2071)
  - Issues: education, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2072)
  - Issues: housing, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2073)
  - Issues: relief, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2074)
  - Issues: Route 1, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2075)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2076)
  - News releases, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2077)
  - Publicity, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2078)
  - Radio, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2079)
  - Republicans, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 2080)
  - Advertising, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 2081)
  - Charter revision, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 2082)
  - Convention, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 2083)
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 2084)
  - Democratic ticket, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 2085)
  - Issues: Assessments, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2086)
  - Issues: education, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2087)
  - Issues: general, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2088)
  - Issues: Hald Trucking Company, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2089)
  - Issues: parking, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2090)
  - Issues: public works, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2091)
  - Issues: recreation, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2092)
  - Legal file, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2093)
  - Miscellaneous: VIII Property, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2094)
  - News releases, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2095-2096)
  - Publicity, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2097)
  - Radio, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2098)
  - Republicans, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2099)
  - Television, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2100)
  - Voting returns, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 2101)
  - Issues, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 2102)
  - Addresses, 1953 (Box 117, Folder 2103)
  - Convention, 1953 (Box 117, Folder 2104)
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2105-2107)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2108-2109)
  - Congratulatory telegrams, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2110)
  - Election results, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2111)
  - Inauguration, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2112)
  - Independents for Lee, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2113)
  - Issues, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2114-2115)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 2116-2117)
  - News clips, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2118-2119)
  - Petition, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2120)
  - Platform, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2121)
  - Publicity, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2122)
  - Radio, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2123)
  - Television, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2124)
  - Ward lists, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 2125)
  - Addresses, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2126)
  - Advertising, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2127)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2128)
  - Congratulatory telegrams, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2129)
  - Convention, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2130)
  - Election returns, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 2131)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2132-2133)
  - News clips, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2134)
  - Publicity, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2135)
  - Republicans, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2136)
  - Surverys and polls, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2137)
  - Television, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2138)
  - Yale cartoon, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 2139)
  - Giaimo, Robert N., 1956 (Box 120, Folder 2140)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 2141)
  - Publications, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 2142)
  - Stevenson-Kefauver, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 2143)
  - Surveys and polls, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 2144)
  - Addresses, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2145)
  - Advertising, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2146)
  - Campaigning data, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2147)
  - Citizens for Lee, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2148)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2149-2150)
  - Congratulatory telegrams, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2151)
  - Convention, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2152)
  - Cook, Edith V., 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2153)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2154)
  - Democratic Town Committee, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2155)
  - Election statistics, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2156)
  - Endorsements, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2157)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2158)
  - News clippings, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2159-2161)
  - Publicity, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2162)
  - Radio, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2163)
  - Surveys and polls, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2164)
  - Television, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 2165)
  - Benton, William, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 2166)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 2167)
  - Charter, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2168)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2169)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2170)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham A., 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2171)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham A.: campaign buttons, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 2172)
  - Addresses, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2173)
  - Advertising, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2174)
  - Campaigning data, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2175)
  - Congratulatory letters and telegrams, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2176)
  - Citizens for Lee, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2177-2178)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2179)
  - Democratic Town Committee, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2180)
  - Election statistics, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2181)
  - Endorsements, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2182)
  - Issues, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2183)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2184-2185)
  - News clippings, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 2186)
  - News releases, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2187-2188)
  - Primary, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2189)
  - Publicity, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2190)
  - Surveys and polls, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2191)
  - Television, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2192)
  - Valenti, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 2193)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2194)
  - Inauguration: John F. Kennedy, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2195)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2196)
  - News clippings, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2197)
  - Pittsburgh Conference, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2198-2200)
  - Pittsburgh Conference: post conference Correspondence, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2201)
  - Pro-Stevenson material, 1960 (Box 123, Folder 2202)
  - Publications, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 2203)
  - Surveys and polls, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 2204)
  - Urban Affairs: cabinet post, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 2205)
  - Addresses, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2206)
  - Advertising, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2207)
  - Citizens for Lee, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2208)
  - Congratulatory messages, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2209)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2210)
  - Election data, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2211)
  - Issues, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2212)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2213-2214)
  - News clippings, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2215)
  - News releases, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2216-2219)
  - Publicity, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2220)
  - Radio, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 2221)
  - Surveys and polls, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 2222)
  - Television, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 2223)
  - Townshend, Henry, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 2224)
  - Valenti, James, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 2225)
  - State Election: Dempsey - Alsop, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 2226)
  - Campaign: general, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2227-2228)
  - Citizens for Lee, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2229)
  - Civil rights, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2230)
  - Convention, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2231)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2232)
  - Election returns, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2233)
  - Form letters, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2234)
  - Inauguration, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2235)
  - Issues, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2236)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2237)
  - News clippings, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 2238)
  - News releases, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2239-2243)
  - Paige, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2244)
  - Prayer ban, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2245)
  - Publicity, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2246)
  - Radio, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2247)
  - Republicans, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2248)
  - Surveys and polls, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2249)
  - Television, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 2250)
  - Wallace, George, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 2251)
  - National convention, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 2252)
  - New Hampshire election returns, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 2253)
  - Surveys and polls, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 2254)
  - Advertising, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2255)
  - Campaign, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2256)
  - Campaigning data, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2257)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2258)
  - Endorsements, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2259)
  - Humphrey and Kennedy, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2260)
  - Issues, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2261)
  - News clippings, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2262)
  - News releases: index, Aug 31 - Sep 24, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 2263)
  - News releases: Sep 25 - Nov 1, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2264-2268)
  - Publicity, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2269)
  - Radio, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2270)
  - Republicans, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2271)
  - Surveys: Waves I - III, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2272)
  - Surveys and polls, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2273)
  - Television, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2274)
  - Top secret, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 2275)
  - Election, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 2276)
  - Acceptance speech, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 2277)
  - Advertising, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2278)
  - Campaigning data, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2279-2280)
  - Citizens for Lee, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2281)
  - Convention, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2282)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2283)
  - Democratic Town Committee, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2284)
  - Election results, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2285)
  - Inauguration, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2286)
  - Kennedy visit, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2287)
  - Mayor Lee's copy, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2288)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2289)
  - News clippings, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2290)
  - News releases, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2291)
  - Publicity, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2292)
  - Radio, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 2293)
  - Republicans: Whitney, Clarence and Hoblitzelle, Wm., 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2294)
  - Students for Lee, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2295)
  - Surveys and polls, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2296)
  - Television, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2297)
  - Surveys and polls, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 2298)
  - Biographical sketch, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 2299)
- Appointment Books, 1944-1976; Series IV
  Extent: 3.75' linear feet (9 boxes).
  This series contains appointment books for Richard C. Lee covering the years 1944 and 1947-1976. They are helpful for researchers interested in identification of the exact times for meetings, conferences, appointments with political associates, wakes, and his attendance of religious and ethnic functions. The appointment books are arranged in chronological order
  - 1944, 1947-1954 1944, 1947-1954 (Box 131, Folder 2300-2304)
  - 1954-1957 1954-1957 (Box 132, Folder 2305-2308)
  - 1957-1959 1957-1959 (Box 133, Folder 2309-2312)
  - 1960-1962 1960-1962 (Box 134, Folder 2313-2316)
  - 1962-1965 1962-1965 (Box 135, Folder 2317-2320)
  - 1965-1967 1965-1967 (Box 136, Folder 2321-2324)
  - 1968-1970 1968-1970 (Box 137, Folder 2325-2328)
  - 1971-1973 1971-1973 (Box 138, Folder 2329-2331)
  - 1974-1976 1974-1976 (Box 139, Folder 2332-2334)
- Photographs, 1947-1969; Series V
  Extent: 2.5 linear feet (6 boxes)
  This series contains chronologically arranged photographs of Lee and New Haven, covering the period 1947-1969. The major proportion of them are from the years 1956-1969 and provide considerable pictorial documentation on Mayor Lee and the course of New Haven redevelopment, from the tearing down of dilapidated old structures to the dedication of new buildings.
  - Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 140, Folder 2335)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 140, Folder 2336)
  - Election, 1951 (Box 140, Folder 2337)
  - Summer: Lee with Odin von Beckgold, 1951 (Box 140, Folder 2338-2340)
  - Yale student demonstration, 1951 (Box 140, Folder 2341)
  - Stevenson, Adlai: in New Haven, 1952 (Box 140, Folder 2342-2343)
  - Truman, Harry S.: in New Haven, 1952 (Box 140, Folder 2344-2346)
  - Campaign, 1953 (Box 140, Folder 2347)
  - Election night, 1953 (Box 140, Folder 2348)
  - Victory celebration, 1953 (Box 140, Folder 2349)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 140, Folder 2350-2353)
  - Supplement to the Report on Springside Home, 1954 (Box 140, Folder 2354-2358)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 140, Folder 2359-2365)
  - Inaugural and miscellaneous, 1956 January-April (Box 140, Folder 2366)
  - Memorial Day Parade, 1956 (Box 140, Folder 2367)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956 June (Box 141, Folder 2368)
  - Miscellaneous and Democratic Rally, 1956 September-October (Box 141, Folder 2369)
  - Democratic Party, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 2370)
  - Groundbreaking ceremonies for new shopping center, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 2371)
  - Saint Bernard's school dedication, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 2372)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957 January-March (Box 141, Folder 2373)
  - Conference with President Eisenhower and Powder House Day, 1957 April (Box 141, Folder 2374)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957 May-July (Box 141, Folder 2375)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957 October (Box 141, Folder 2376)
  - Election day, 1957 November (Box 141, Folder 2377)
  - Election day and miscellaneous, 1957 November (Box 141, Folder 2378)
  - Footguard's Ball and miscellaneous, 1958 February - March (Box 141, Folder 2379)
  - Truman, Harry S. in New Haven and Miscellaneous, 1958 April - May (Box 141, Folder 2380)
  - Sheraton announcement and miscellaneous, 1958 July - October (Box 141, Folder 2381)
  - Look Magazine, 1958 December (Box 141, Folder 2382-2383)
  - Ingall's Skating Rink, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2384)
  - Lee with Boards of Aldermen and Finance, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2385)
  - Lee visits Winchester School, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2386)
  - Mayor in office, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2387)
  - New Haven photographs, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2388-2389)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 141, Folder 2390)
    See also: Oversize Materials
  - Miscellaneous and Footguard Ball and Dinner, 1959 January - February (Box 141, Folder 2391)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 March - August (Box 141, Folder 2392-2394)
  - Police Awards Ceremony, football game, and Columbus Day Parade, 1959 October (Box 141, Folder 2395)
  - Columbus Day parade, 1959 October (Box 141, Folder 2396)
  - WNHC television studio an opening of Railroad diesel shop, 1959 October (Box 141, Folder 2397)
  - Opening of Railroad Diesel Shop, 1959 October (Box 141, Folder 2398)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 October - November (Box 141, Folder 2399)
  - New Haven photographs, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 2400-2401)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 2402)
  - Miscellaneous and Wilbur Cross-Notre Dame Game, 1960 February - March (Box 141, Folder 2403)
  - Wilbur Cross-Notre Dame Game, 1960 March (Box 142, Folder 2404)
  - Saint Patrick's Day parade, 1960 March (Box 142, Folder 2405-2406)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960 April (Box 142, Folder 2407-2408)
  - New Haven Photographs, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 2409-2413)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 January - March (Box 142, Folder 2414)
  - Wilbur Cross-Hartford basketball game, 1961 March (Box 142, Folder 2415)
  - Saint Patrick's Day parade, 1961 March (Box 142, Folder 2416)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 April (Box 142, Folder 2417)
  - Yale honorary degree recipient, 1961 June (Box 142, Folder 2418)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 June (Box 142, Folder 2419)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 July (Box 142, Folder 2420-2422)
  - New Haven Photographs, 1961 (Box 142, Folder 2423)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962 March (Box 142, Folder 2424-2426)
  - Parking garage, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 2427-2428)
  - Stiles and Morse Colleges, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 2429-2430)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 January - October (Box 142, Folder 2431-2433)
  - Election night, 1963 November (Box 142, Folder 2434-2435)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 2436)
  - New Haven photographs, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 2437-2438)
  - Wooster Square and Dixwell Projects, 1963 (Box 142, Folder 2439)
  - Wooster Square Project, 1964 June (Box 143, Folder 2440)
  - Portraits, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 2441-2447)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 2448)
  - New Haven photographs, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 2449)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965 August - October (Box 143, Folder 2450-2451)
  - Vice President Humphrey visits New Haven, 1965 October (Box 143, Folder 2452-2453)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 2454)
  - Family photograph: Tara, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 2455)
  - Inauguration and opening of I-91, 1966 January (Box 143, Folder 2456)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 January - May (Box 143, Folder 2457-2459)
  - Meet the Press, 1966 June (Box 143, Folder 2460-2461)
  - Yale Drama School Architecture Address and Mayor at Prince Street School, 1966 June (Box 143, Folder 2462)
  - Dedication: Ribicoff Cottages, 1966 June (Box 143, Folder 2463)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 July (Box 143, Folder 2464)
  - K-4 groundbreaking at Newhallville, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 2465-2468)
  - "The Mayor and The Changing City" and groundbreaking for Labor Temple, 1966 August (Box 143, Folder 2469)
  - Groundbreaking for Labor Temple, 1966 August (Box 143, Folder 2470-2471)
  - Crawford Manor Dedication, 1966 September (Box 143, Folder 2472-2474)
  - Crawford Manor Dedication, 1966 September (Box 144, Folder 2475-2479)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 September - October (Box 144, Folder 2480)
  - Chapel Square opening, 1966 October (Box 144, Folder 2481)
  - Chapel Square opening and miscellaneous, 1966 October (Box 144, Folder 2482)
  - Miscellaneous and Christmas week, 1966 November - December (Box 144, Folder 2483)
  - Christmas week and miscellaneous, 1966 December (Box 144, Folder 2484)
  - Crawford Manor, 1966 (Box 144, Folder 2485-2486)
  - Kline Science Center, 1966 (Box 144, Folder 2487-2488)